Introducing Kwiksher
Kwiksher LLC, maker of Kwik — a Photoshop plugin for creating retina-quality
interactive books, magazines and apps for iOS/Android without code — and Kutt,
a UI-export plugin. Founded May 2011 by Alex Souza in Florida; under new
management since September 2014. Official Corona Labs partner.
"You are an artist not a code jockey. Kwik unleashes your creativity letting
Photoshop plugin
interactive books
storybook apps
iOS
Android
no-code
digital publishing
Kwik
Kutt
No-code app creation directly from Photoshop
Retina-quality interactive books/magazines/apps
Official Corona Labs partner
Introducing Kwiksher